Ashley Kuhn

Phone: 949-813-8304 | Email: ashleymkuhn1@gmail.com | Mission Viejo, CA

Summary

- Enthusiastic UX/UI designer with a background in geospatial technology.
- Successful in a collaborative environment, with experience in team management, leading meetings, creating documentation and conducting training.
- Self-motivated learner, excited to share and improve my skills with a great team.
- Previous experience has included fieldwork, office work and remote work, providing a wide range
 of perspectives on how user interfaces in websites, software, and applications can be improved
 for a variety of different use cases.

Technical Skills

UX/UI: Figma, XD, Miro | Low-Fidelity Prototyping, High-Fidelity Mockups, UI Pattern Libraries, Heuristic

Evaluation, Human-Centered Design, Web Accessibility, User Interviews & Testing

Design: Adobe Suite - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop | Blender **Web Development:** VSCode - HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript

ArcGIS: Desktop, Pro, Online, Dashboard, Field Apps

UAV: Part 107 License | DJI GO 4, Pix4D, Maps Made Easy, SiteScan

Terrestrial LIDAR Software: Leica Cyclone 360, Leica 3DR, FARO Scene, Matterport

Experience

Acquisition Operations Lead

November 2019 - September 2022

Aethon Aerial Solutions

San Diego, CA

- Promoted from UAV Pilot & Lidar Technician to Acquisition Operations Lead.
- Oversaw 10+ field teams' data acquisition efforts, ensuring all equipment, crews, and project details were prepared.
- Lead daily safety meetings for the UAV pilots.
- Responsible for project tracking and scheduling, utilizing mapping software such as ArcPro and Google Earth.
- Managed terrestrial lidar projects, responsible for keeping track of the field data, post-processing, and quality checking the final deliverables.
- Created training documentation and led training presentations for new staff.

GIS Field Technician D&W Consulting

June 2017 - November 2019

Irvine, CA

- Consulted with the Irvine Company to create GIS maps and 3D models for over 40 retail shopping centers.
- Collaborated with operations, sales, construction, and design managers to iterate on map designs and determine data collection needs.

GIS Analyst Intern

County of San Luis Obispo

April 2016 – June 2017 San Luis Obispo, CA

- Developed thematic maps and graphics for community plans and public meetings.
- Interpreted and digitized archaeological surveys, biological reports, and environmental impact reports in ArcMap.

Education

UX/UI Certificate: University of California, Irvine

Graduated January 2023

An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to design thinking, user experience, user interface design, and web design.

Bachelor of Science in Anthropology and Geography, Minor in City and Regional Planning: California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo

Graduated March 2017